Guide to the Ian P. Watt Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, Accession ARCH-1994-106
  - Krajka, Wieslaw (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Krajka Typescript (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - "L" (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Laburthe"Tolra, Philippe (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - 18 Offprints now (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Language (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Lean, David (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Leavis, F.R. and Q.D. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Lesser, Wendy (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Literacy Talk (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Literacy (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Literacy: Notes and References (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Little, Brown and Company (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - "M" (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Modern Language Association [MLA] (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Mursia, Ugo (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - "N" (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Najder, Zdislaw (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Najder, Zdislaw: up to 1975. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Najder, Zdislaw: 1975"1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Najder, Zdislaw: 1978 on. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - NEA: The Bibliography (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Napier, Sir William Francis Patrick (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Nied, David (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Norwich cuttings (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Norwich: Practical Criticism (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Handouts"Historical and Sociological Criticism. Bibliography. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - "O" (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Offprint Lists (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Offprints (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Opinions on Manuscripts (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - "P" (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Publishing Permission: Conrad. (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Publisher's Correspondence"Requests for Reviews. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Publisher's Reports. Current. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Publisher's Reports. Until 1970. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Reprint Correspondence. Current. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Reprint Correspondence. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Poland (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Porter, Catherine (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - PMLA"Fielding Article. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - On Periodic Sentence. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - "R" (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - "R" (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - "R" (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Raleigh, John Henry (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Richardson, Matthew (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Bourgeois Culture and Popular Culture, by L. del G. Destreri (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence about writings: "Rise of the Novel" (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - "Rise of the Novel". Errata. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - "Rise of the Novel". 1991 Rewrite. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - "Rise of the Novel". Reviews. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - "Rise of the Novel". Reviews. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - "Rise of the Novel". Reviews continued. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - "Rise of the Novel". Translations. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - "Rise of the Novel". References. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Queneau, Raymond (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Quinones: Literacy. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - "Rise of the Novel". Correspondence with Chatto and Windus. (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - "Rise of the Novel". Correspondence with Chatto and Windus. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Richards, I.A. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Richetti, John J. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Riggs, David (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Rogers, Pat (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Roland, Charly and Jacqueline (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Rosse, Jim (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Royalties: Cambridge University Press. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Royalties: Cambridge University Press. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Royalties: "Rise of the Novel". (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Royalties (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Royalties; Reprints. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - "Rise of the Novel""University of California Press: Sales. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - "Rise of the Novel""University of California Press: Correspondence. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - "S" (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - "S" (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Said, Edward (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Schorer, Mark (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Schwartz, Daniel R. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Schwendener, Peter (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Scurfield, George (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Searle, John (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Secret Agent (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Seuil (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Seuil: Taxes and Receipts. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Sex (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Shakespeare. Phi Beta Kappa Talk. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Shakespeare. Phi Beta Kappa Talk. (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Shakespeare's Wisdom; Notes. (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Shinagel, Michael (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Skenazy, Paul (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Solomon, Louise (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Sherry, Norman (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Smith, Henry Nash (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Tim Mason (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Sosna, Mort (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Stanford Sierra Camp (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Stange, Bob (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Stegner, Wallace (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Steinmetz, George (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Sterne Edition [The Florida Edition] (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Sterne Memorial (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Sterne"Review (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Stockwell, Jeff (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Summers, Joseph (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Szczypien, Jean M. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - "T" (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - "T" (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - [Talks and Teachings]
    - Brown Conference; My Paper etc. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Miami Talk: Conrad. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - 1984"Alumni: New York (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - New York Conference: Talk. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Wuthering Heights. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Silence (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - 18 Society: French Revolution (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Humanities 63: Rousseau (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Prospectuses (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Ph.D. Orals"Mine. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Stanford Departmental Affairs. 1976" (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - 303C Current Lecture. (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - 303C: Class Lists Assignments (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Current Lecture 134"234 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Winter 1991"Course Records (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Conrad"San Francisco (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - San Francisco"Conrad (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - "Heart of Darkness" (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Seminar on Joseph Conrad and Colonialism (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Orals; Reading Lists. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Stanford Marklists (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - English 30; 1987. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Berkeley"Victorian Lectures. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Love and the Novel (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - [Other Projects]
    - King Cnut (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Mirrors (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Project Stories etc. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Berkeley"Negotiations; English Chairs. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Oxford University Press (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Time (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Todorov etc. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Todorov, Tzvetan (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - 2nd Thoughts"Japan (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Monterey Talk: Annotation Conrad (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Johnson (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Alumni Talk (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - "Angry Young Man" (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - English in the Future University (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Arts Club (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Fanny Hill (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Foot Hill Talk (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Gondal Poems (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Bronson Festschrift, Letters. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - "Hero as Problem" (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - "Gothic Time", current version. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Tanner, Tony (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Terre Haute (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Thistlewaite, Frank (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Todorov, Tzvetan (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Tolstoy, Leo (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Tordoff, John (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Toth, Susan Allen (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - State Papers; Personal"Watt. (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - University [current]. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Offers, academic. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Bio"Bibliography"Materials [since 1978] (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - "V" (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - VB"AHM (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - VB"Checking Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - VB"Working Papers [1970] (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Victorian Novel [Oxford University Press] (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Victorian Novel: Reviews and Correspondence (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Victorian Novel"Permissions (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Villa Serbelloni (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Humanities 63"Voltaire (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Wollaeger, Mark (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Trist, Eric (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - "W" (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Walwyn, Kim Scott (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Watt, Ian P. (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Talk Summeries (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Arts and Humanities Citation Index"Ian Watt. (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Watt, Tom and Renee (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Donne"Essay (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - "Effects of Print" (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - "The Novel and its Reader 1719"1754" (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Chapter One (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Chapter Two (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Chapter Two (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Past Drafts, Notes (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Chapter Three; old drafts and notes. (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Chapter Three (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Chapter Three; Final Version. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Chapter Four (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Treatment for later Chapter (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous: Printed Man (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Siam Notes (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Oral Version of "Three Myths of the Kwai". (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Texas"Kwai (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Kwai"Revisited [Materials] (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Holiday Version and BBC Version. (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Singapore (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Japan Stuff; Miscellaneous. (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - P.O.W (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Poems (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - "Shamela"[Fielding] (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Current Talks"L.A. (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - "Pope as Poet" (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - McGill Talk (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - "Mind in Prose"[Materials] (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - "The Knowledge of Silence" (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Dover, typescript on return to, 1945 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Berkeley, Eng. 44B, Shakespeare, lecture notes, undated (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - "Shakespeare's Wisdom: An Approach,"typescript article (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Enlightenment Lectures 303C, undated (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Kwai, talk at Stanford Humanities Center, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Kwai"Japan Rewrite (outline) (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - P.O.W.: War History: photocopy of pages from The War against Japan, Volume V, by S. Woodburn Kirby (1969) and clippings, 1983"84 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Kwai – Photos, 1945, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Toosey, Foreman and Bottomley 1966"87 [contains Watt's articles on Kwai, correspondence about Sir Philip Toosey, other source materials, and clippings] (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Grace A. Tanner Lecture; Drafts, not current. (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Tanner Lectures, Correspondence with Eugene T. Woolf, etc., 1980"85 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Grace A. Tanner Lecture in Human Values, The Humanities on the River Kwai by Ian Watt, 1981, published version (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Kwai"Tanner Lectures (Utah) – notes, correspondence (including P. Toosey and J. Coast), 1967"84 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Kwai Talk 1985 – typescript, articles, correspondence (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Kwai Talk 1985 – photographs (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Kwai"Cedar City (Utah) talk – typescript, notes, copies of documents (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Kwai – miscellaneous items and notes (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Hobday Negatives [half"tones for printing purposes, not film negatives] (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - "Humanities on the River Kwai"– newsprint article and correspondence, 1982 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Foreman, Carl, Correspondence (copy of his letter to The Observer about Watt's article, 1968, and his refusal to allow use of, 1981) (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Toosey, Philip, Correspondence (with and about Toosey), 1967"82 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Sam Spiegel, clipping 1988 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Letters regarding Kwai, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Coast, John"Correspondence regarding Coast's work on his film"Return to the River Kwai"along with related Watt's correspondence with other people and a few articles and note, 1967"69 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Kwai talk – Stanford Alumni Version (drafts), 1982 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Association of Indians in America"Talk (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Bridge over the Kwai [Original Full Version and Correspondence] (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Siam"Addresses and Correspondence (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Kwai Myth; Portland Version. (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Glover"Talk Kiwanies (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Kwai"French Version (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Kwai"French Version [Photocopy] (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Kwai and Humanities [1983] (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Almayer's Folly [Final Version] (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Almayer's Folly [Correspondence] (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Reid, S.W. [Almayer's Folly] (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - A Folly; [Edited Version] (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Almayer's Folly [Final Copy 2] (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Quinn, John (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Xeroxes used for Almayer Edition (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Almayer's Folly: Xeroxes (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Almayer's Folly; Current Notes (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Almayer's Folly; Notes of Others, Letters. (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Almayer's Folly; Final Copy 3. (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - River Kwai [Correspondence] (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Almayer's Folly (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Almayer's Folly: Introduction 1984. (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Almayer's Folly Introduction. (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Almayer's Folly: Original Introduction. (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Kwai"Letters, etc. (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Myth"Kwai; Portland Version (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Almayer's Folly; December 19, Copy (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Bliss's Corrections (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Almayer's Folly (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Almayer's Folly, Introduction I. (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Almayer's Folly, Introductions II. (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Almayer's Folly, Introduction III. (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Almayer's Folly, Introduction IV. (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Almayer's Folly, Introduction V. (Box 27, Folder 14)
    - Almayer's Folly, Introduction VI. (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - VII. The Novel (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Almayer's Folly, Introduction VIII. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Almayer's Folly, Collected Edition IX. (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Almayer's Folly, This Edition X. (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Almayer's Folly, corrected up to 1982 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Don Juan, [Julie's Copy] (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Don Juan [1988 Duplicate] (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Myth 3 To Translate (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Don Juan [Working Copy] (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Xeroxes of Myth Chapters (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Myth 2 "Don Quixote" (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Myth 3 Sept. 1988 Draft (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Myth 3 Don Juan [Top Current Copy] (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Myth 3 Death (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Myth 3"D 2 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Myth 3: Bibliography. (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Myth 3: All Saints Day (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Myth 3: Current Notes (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Myth 3: Don Juan; Xeroxes 1988 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Myth 3: To Add. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Baycroft; Notes. (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Individualism: Current (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Myth 4 [Draft] (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Myth: Chapter 4; Notes. (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Myth: Chapter 4; Xeroxes. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Myth: Chapter 4; Tirso. (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Myth in general: Offprints. (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Myth 7.4: Notes to use. (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Myth 7 [1] (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Myth 7 [Present] (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Myth 7.1; Notes to use (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Myth; Notes 7 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Myth; 7.3 Faustus. (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Myth; 7.5; Draft (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Sulaca Map (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Fillingham, Lydia (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Nostromo; Cambridge University Press (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Nostromo Book"Final I (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Nostromo"As sent. (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Nostromo"April 1987 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Nostromo: Chapter I; Typing I. (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Nostromo; Publishing History (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Nostromo; Reception Letters (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Nostromo"Reviews (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Nostromo Proofs (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Nostromo: 3.1; Annotation (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Nostromo: Chapter I. and Notes (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Nostromo; Front Matter (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Nostromo"Notes; Front Matter (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Masterman: Xeroxes (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Nostromo: Chapter 3; Notes, Influences. (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Nostromo: Xeroxes (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Nostromo: Geography, History and Sources. (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Nostromo: Chapter 3; History and Politics. (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Nostromo: Eastwick; Xeroxes. (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Nostromo, Chapter 1, Xeroxes, Notes (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Nostromo: Chapter 2, Section 1. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Nostromo: History and Geography (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Nostromo: Edward Said (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Nostromo: Cuttings (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Nostromo: Notes by me on others. (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Nostromo: Ian Watt, Chapter 4. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Jean Franco: On Nostromo (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Nostromo"Treasure. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Richardson: Irony [1] (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Richardson: Irony [2] (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Richardson: Irony [3] (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Publishers and Sinners: Reviewers, "Rise of the Novel" Time and Gothic (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Publishers and Sinners [2] (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Publishers and Sinners [3] (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Jane Austen: Cady and Watt (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - "Sense and Sensibility"[Final Draft] (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Kwai; Myth, Tanner. (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Seminar"Final Draft and Corespondence (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Tristram Shandy: Comic Syntax: Notes (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Arilles 18 Gothic (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Arilles 18 Gothic [2] (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Arilles 18 Gothic [3] (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Watt Articles. Realism, Arts in Society (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Ian Watt Articles: Realism [2] (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Robinson Crusoe as Myth [1] (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Robinson Crusoe as Myth [2] (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - "The Knowledge of Silence" (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - "L'institution Du Compte Rendu" (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - "The Naming of Characters in Defoe, Richardson, and Fielding (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Myth; Robinson Crusoe, Chapter 5 [Final] (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Myth; Chapter 6 [Final] (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Myth; Chapter 2 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Myth; Don Juan, Chapter 3 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Myth; Chapter 4 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Myth; Chapter 3, 1988 Revision (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Myth; Don Juan VI (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Myth 3, Don Juan to add (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Myth; Title Pages [Current] (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Myth; Research: Notes and Bibliography (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Myth; Plans, Acknowledgments. (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Myth Book"Abrams (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Myth 1; Bibliography (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Myth; Rejected Pages 1 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Myth; University of California Press"Contract 1966 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Myth; Introduction, Chapter 1 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Myth"Preface (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Myth: Recent Letters (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Myth; Format & Style (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Myth; to add (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Myth; Report on Myth Book, Letters (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Myth; Chapter 7 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Myth cuttings etc. (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Myth cuttings etc. [2] (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Myth cuttings etc. [3] (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Myth cuttings etc. [4] (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Myth cuttings etc. [5] (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - ADE"Talk [Piano] 1977 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Review: French Lieutenants Woman (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - John Fowles etc. (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Norwich Article (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Piano Piece and Norwich [1] (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Piano Piece and Norwich [2] (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Allen and Gindin [Economist] (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Battestin"Review (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Oral Dickens (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - The Consequences of Literacy (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Realism and Faust (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Review"Conrad, Jerry Allen (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Milan Kundera (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - "Spender on Trial" (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - John Fowles; "The French Lieutenant's Woman" (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Laurence Sterne (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Critical Review; Faustus (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Review: Bate/Johnson (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Review: Melville (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Modern Language Notes (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Modern Philology (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Mothers of the Novel (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Jane Austen Paper (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Conrad Review (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Watt, Reviews [1] (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Watt, Reviews [2] (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Watt, Reviews [3] (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Watt, Reviews [4] (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Watt; La Critique Realiste [1] (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Watt; La Critique Realiste [2] (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Review of "Rise of the Novel" (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Watt: Richardson (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - "Second Thoughts", Correspondence (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - "Second Thoughts", Materials (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Second Thoughts, Drafts (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Sigi Notes, Henning und so weiter (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Myth IV, Xeroxes 1"2 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Myth IV, Recent Texts (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Myth, Xeroxes (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Myth IV, to add (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Myth IV, Bibliography (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Myth IV, Xeroxes 3 & 4 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Myth IV, Xeroxes (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Myth, Chapter 4 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Myth"Articles, Chapter 4 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Counter"Reformation (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Myth IV, Counter"Reformation (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Myth IV, Draft, Corrections (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Myth IV, Draft [8/5/91] (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Myth IV, Watt's Notes (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Myth IV, Faust Xeroxes (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Myth IV, Cuttings & Offprints (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Myth IV, Additions etc. (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Myth IV, Individualism (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Myth IV, the first three (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Myth IV (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Myth V, Defoe Notes (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Myth V, Robinson Crusoe, Draft [7/91] (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Myth V, Clipping (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Myth V, Recent Xeroxes (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Myth V, Defoe, Xeroxes and Clippings (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Myth V, Offprints (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Myth V, Crusoe, Xeroxes 1987 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - 315"Robinson Crusoe (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Myth V, Offprints used for Notes (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Myth V, Defoe, Xerox (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Robinson Crusoe [1983] (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Robinson Crusoe"Talk (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Myth, Chapter 5, [Early Draft] (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Robinson Crusoe, Retype [1991] (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Myth, Chapter 5: Robinson Crusoe, to add (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Robinson Crusoe [1950"1980] (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Myth, Chapter 5: Drafts, Notes (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Chapter IV, First Draft (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Chapter IV, Draft (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Myth 4, to add (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Myth 5, Notes (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Myth 6.1 My Notes, Top Drafts (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Myth 6, Romantic Apotheosis (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Myth 6.4 Xeroxes and Notes (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Myth 6 Don Juan and Don Quixote (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - Myth 6.5 Notes actually used (Box 44, Folder 16)
    - Myth 6, Robinson Crusoe, Notes (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Myth 6, Robinson Crusoe, Rousseau; Notes used (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Myth 6, Goethe, Xeroxes used for Notes (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Myth 6, Vico, Xeroxes (Box 45, Folder 2)